http://www.sdcc.edu/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY - San Diego Christian College
Readying for your return: Fall Return to campus plan - Click Here
MORE ABOUT SDCC
WHY SDCCASSOCIATIONS & ACCREDITATIONDOCTRINAL STATEMENTCOMMUNITY COVENANTPRIVACY POLICYDISCLOSURES
UNDERGRADUATE
Aviation, BSBiblical Studies, BABiological Science, BSBusiness Administration, BSCommunication, BAEnglish, BAInterdisciplinary Studies, BAKinesiology and Rehabilitation Science, BSLiberal Studies, BSPsychology, BA
ONLINE PROGRAMS
Business Management, BSChristian Ministries, BACommunication, BAHuman Development, BALeadership, BSLiberal Studies, AAPsychology, BAOnline Bachelor’s Degree Emphasis and Minor Options
GRADUATE PROGRAMS
Leadership, MSTeaching, MATeaching CredentialCombined Credential and Master’s Program for Teaching
CONCURRENT ENROLLMENTREGISTRAR
Admissions
Undergraduate AdmissionsOnline AdmissionsGraduate AdmissionsConcurrent EnrollmentInternational Students
Tuition
UndergraduateOnline ProgramsGraduate Programs
AthleticsStudent Life
Student Affairs
Global Missions
LIBRARY
VisitApply
Search for:
ABOUT
MORE ABOUT SDCC
WHY SDCC
ASSOCIATIONS & ACCREDITATION
DOCTRINAL STATEMENT
COMMUNITY COVENANT
PRIVACY POLICY
LEADERSHIP
2021 Spring
Loading...
Alternate Subject:
--None--
houseboat
cruise ship
airplane
Best Time To Call:
More Info:
*All Form Flelds are Required
ADMIN LOGIN
STUDENT LOGIN
x
PRIVACY POLICY
Our commitment to privacy
Protecting your privacy is important, and we strive to keep your personal information confidential as well as the privacy of our website visitors. Since our work involves sensitive lead form information, data security is paramount.
Please take a moment to read our privacy policy to learn how we handle your personal information.
Why we collect personal information
This site collects and uses personal information to provide you with requested information regarding products and services, in addition to providing up-to-date announcements, events and other information.
When we disclose personal information
We will not share, sell, rent or disclose your personal information without your advance permission, unless so ordered by a court of law or if we deem disclosure is necessary for the public interest. Information submitted to us is only available to those employees who manage the information. We adhere to FERPA Act regulations, which afford students certain rights with respect to their education records. FERPA overrides any other privacy policy in regards to current and past students. See our FERPA Policy for more information.
How we protect personal information
This site uses physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard personal information. We constantly re-evaluate and deploy new technologies to enhance security.
This site uses secure encryption on all web pages where sensitive information is required. When submitting sensitive information, you must use a browser such as Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later. This protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it is transmitted over the Internet.
Collecting other information
Generally, we don’t collect personal information when you browse our website. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us what type of computer and operating system you use. Like many websites, we use “cookie” technology. When you connect to portions of our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. These cookies do not reveal personal information. They help us understand which parts of our website are most popular, where our visitors go and how long they spend there.
We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make regular site improvements. We urge you to protect your personal data whenever you are on the Internet: Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers and make sure that you are using a secure browser.
This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. Please review this policy regularly.
Loading...
Alternate Subject:
--None--
houseboat
cruise ship
airplane
Best Time To Call:
More Info:
2020 San Diego Christian College. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy. Brand by BLVR
San Diego Christian College | 200 Riverview Parkway Santee, CA 92071
Readying for Your Return: Fall Return to Campus Plan - CLICK HERE
